http://www.ultimateknicks.com/privacypolicy.asp

Salary Sites
Salaries (HoopsHype.com)
Salary Cap FAQ (Larry Coon)
Trade Sites
Trade Checker (RealGM.com)
Trade Machine (ESPN.com)
Privacy Policy
UltimateKnicks, which operates the public website at https://www.UltimateKnicks.com/ ("UltimateKnicks.com"), is committed to protecting the privacy and security of our online visitors. We want you to understand the measures we have taken to ask for and use information properly, and to make UltimateKnicks.com a safe environment for everyone. We therefore strongly advise our visitors to read through and understand this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy").
We may update it from time to time to address new issues or reflect changes on our website. Please refer to this Privacy Policy regularly, and if you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@UltimateKnicks.com.
The UltimateKnicks Public Discussion Forums:
UltimateKnicks.com makes public discussion forums available to our visitors ("UltimateKnicks Forums") and these have grown to be extremely popular places for sports fans to meet and chat. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. Consequently you should exercise extreme caution when deciding whether to disclose your private and/or personal information on the UltimateKnicks Forums, which we strongly advise against.
To the extent that the UltimateKnicks Forums provide visitors an opportunity to post and exchange information, ideas and opinions ("Posts"), BE ADVISED THAT ULTIMATEKNICKS.COM DOES NOT AS A PRACTICE SCREEN, EDIT OR REVIEW THE POSTS PRIOR TO THEIR APPEARANCE ON ULTIMATEKNICKS.COM, and the Posts do not necessarily reflect the views of UltimateKnicks.com. UltimateKnicks.com reserves the right to monitor all the Posts and to remove any which we consider offensive or otherwise in violation of our Terms of Use. Please read these Terms of Use according to which UltimateKnicks.com will in no way be responsible or liable for the Posts.
Here are more legal notices regarding the Posts: You must have all necessary rights in and to all the Posts you provide and all material they contain; your Posts must not infringe any proprietary or other rights of third parties; your Posts must not contain any viruses or other contaminating or destructive devices or features; your Posts must not contain any defamatory, indecent, offensive, tortious or otherwise unlawful material or content; and your Posts must not be used to carry out or solicit any unlawful activity and/or be used to make commercial solicitations. Also, you authorize UltimateKnicks.com and/or others to use all or part of your Posts in any manner, format or medium that UltimateKnicks.com or such other parties see fit; and you shall have no claim or other recourse against UltimateKnicks.com for infringement of any proprietary right in your Posts. Violating these terms will subject the visitor to investigation and enforcement to ensure compliance; personal information may be used and/or disclosed by UltimateKnicks.com in this process, to the extent necessary to ensure a safe, secure and enjoyable experience at UltimateKnicks.com. Also, we will keep your Posts on UltimateKnicks.com even after your stop actively contributing or even after you close your membership account in the UltimateKnicks Forums.
Posts do not constitute personally identifiable information you share with us privately, and therefore UltimateKnicks.com has no obligation to remove them.
As a practice, we will not remove your Posts unless there is another reason, besides you simply closing your account.
In addition, please review the below information about registering for a membership account in the UltimateKnicks Forums.
Information Visitors Provide To Us:
UltimateKnicks.com endeavors to provide you quality information that is tailored to your needs. In order to do that we may sometimes ask you for information so that we can provide the kind of content you want, when you want it. We want to customize our website for you so that it meets your needs as fully as possible - this includes customizing articles, discussions, banners and more. We may ask you to register or provide personal information when you visit certain areas of UltimateKnicks.com, enter a contest, play games, complete surveys, subscribe to a service or newsletter, submit content or ask us for information.
We only collect personally identifiable information from you when you voluntarily submit it. Providing your personal information to UltimateKnicks.com is optional. If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use our website but you may not have access to certain areas and/or types of information.
We want you to be fully informed that as part of registering for a membership account in the UltimateKnicks Forums, you would need to give us a valid email address.
This is necessary for setting up and activating your UltimateKnicks Forums username and password, and sending you important notifications from time to time.
Without your email address, we cannot complete this process.
However, you can still browse the UltimateKnicks.com website freely and you won't be limited by not giving your email address EXCEPT THAT you will NOT be able to have an active membership account in the UltimateKnicks Forums, which is what enables you to create and upload Posts on the UltimateKnicks Forums.
If you don't register, you can still view all of the topics and Posts on the UltimateKnicks Forums.
If you decide to share your email address in order to register for a membership account in the UltimateKnicks Forums, it will be privately and securely stored in a UltimateKnicks.com-controlled database that will never be visible or accessible to the general public. We will never share your email address with any other person or company simply because we collected it for registration. Email addresses will be kept only by UltimateKnicks.com and only for the purpose of being able to properly activate and administer the UltimateKnicks Forums accounts.
If you do choose to register for a membership account in the UltimateKnicks Forums, and if you are eligible for one, you will get an initial email to confirm the email address you gave us. You can always decide later to deactivate your account. For those individuals reasonably identified as visiting UltimateKnicks.com from the European Economic Area or the State of California in the United States who want to register for membership in the UltimateKnicks Forums, please note that we take special care to walk you through the registration process so that you are fully informed about freely and simply giving your consent to provide your email address and, potentially, your name, and how to later deactivate your account and delete your information if you wish to do so. The same will be true of any other sign-up or registration process on UltimateKnicks.com. If you inquire about how UltimateKnicks.com has kept your information, we will respond to you within a short period of time with an official, documented disclosure of the corresponding information we have securely stored. Again, UltimateKnicks.com does not sell or share your information at present, and will never do so unless we change this Privacy Policy and also get your own consent for sharing information after a clear request outlining how the information would be shared if you do agree to provide consent. Until then, your information will be used solely for purposes of registering and maintaining the UltimateKnicks.com account itself.
Also, we make it easy for you to unsubscribe from the daily newsletter from UltimateKnicks.com, "Heads Up," or other information-related communications or services for which you may register, and to remove your registration and any related communications. For example, you will find an Unsubscribe link at the bottom of each Heads Up email. Simply click that link to unsubscribe and have your information deleted. In other cases, you may have a direct email contact who can process your request to remove your account and delete personally identifiable information after you previously registered with UltimateKnicks.com.
Please note that the information above describes UltimateKnicks.com's practices, which may differ from third-party advertisers.
Third-Party Advertising:
UltimateKnicks.com uses outside, third-party advertising companies to serve ads and potentially collect information when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to our website and other websites, in order to provide advertisements on our website, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. Their ads may also contain cookies. If you would like more information about this subject, please review the rest of this Privacy Policy. And to know your choices concerning not having this information used by these companies, please review the information at the following link:
http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
What Are Cookies?
The use of cookies is common in the Internet industry; you'll find them used on UltimateKnicks.com as you will at other major websites. "Cookies" are small text files written to your computer. They make our website easier for you to use because they save your preferences while you are at our website. Cookies also help us know which areas are your favorites, which need a bit of improvement and what technologies and Internet services our visitors are using. Knowing this information helps us continually improve the online experience for our visitors and members. In the course of serving advertisements to this website, a third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. The non-personally identifiable information tracked with cookies is anonymous and is not used to identify, or lead us back to, any particular visitor. Visitors of UltimateKnicks.com may have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preferences (most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies).
While browsing through UltimateKnicks.com you may get cookies from our advertisers or sponsors. UltimateKnicks.com and its affiliated websites do not control these cookies. In delivering advertising on UltimateKnicks.com, individuals who are reasonably identified as visiting UltimateKnicks.com from the European Economic Area will be notified about cookies and/or asked for their consent to gather any other information if needed to run one or more advertising campaigns.
Choice/Opt-Out:
If we need to collect any information from you other than cookies, we will ask you in plain and simple language and you'll have an easy, straightforward and uncomplicated way to decline providing any of that kind of information if you wish.
For all of our website's visitors, we will not share your email address with third-party marketing entities without your express consent, including easy-to-understand language asking if you specifically give consent for this. Also if you do register for any of the UltimateKnicks.com programs or services but decide later that you do not want your data shared with third parties for marketing or promotional purposes, you can always opt out at any time by sending us an email at info@UltimateKnicks.com. Please also provide your registration details including first name, last name, street address, city, state, postal code and country. This information will only be used by us to make sure your wishes are respected.
We Protect Children's Privacy:
We are working hard to provide you with the best information and the highest quality interaction on the Internet in an environment that is safe. And we recognize a special obligation to protect personal information obtained from children. In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"), we have adopted the following policies to keep kids safe:
1. We will NOT knowingly collect, use or distribute personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 without prior verifiable consent from a parent or guardian.
2. Personally identifiable information we collect from children under the age of 13 will be used solely by UltimateKnicks.com or its agents for internal purposes only, and will not be sold or otherwise distributed to third parties.
3. We will NOT knowingly allow a child under the age of 13 access to the UltimateKnicks Forums or other services within UltimateKnicks.com that would allow them to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable consent from a parent or guardian.
4. We will NOT knowingly ask a child under the age of 13 to divulge more information than is needed to participate in any activity, game or service.
5. We will NOT knowingly provide any direct link to websites that are unsuitable for children.
6. UltimateKnicks.com will not advertise on any website that does not comply with the regulations set forth under COPPA.
7. We will advise children under the age of 13 that they MUST obtain permission from their parent or guardian before sharing ANY personal information.
8. Upon request, UltimateKnicks.com will provide a parent or guardian with a description of the information that may have been provided about their child under the age of 13 during a registration process for a program or service offered by our website. UltimateKnicks.com only asks for such a child's personal information if it is necessary to participate in the program or service. The website's administrators also have access to the registration data but they are only used for website maintenance. Registration data that are provided about children are not used for marketing and are never shared with any other party. If you would like to view your child's registration data, request a change or request that we delete any of your child's personal information, please send an email to info@UltimateKnicks.com which includes your child's first and last name, and your first and last name.
UltimateKnicks.com urges parents and guardians to instruct their children to never give out their real names, addresses or phone numbers without permission when using the Internet.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy related to children, please email us at info@UltimateKnicks.com.
Notification And Verifiable Parental Consent:
Before any personally identifiable information is collected from anyone under the age of 13, we require the parent or guardian to provide verifiable parental consent, such as an email to UltimateKnicks.com. When such verifiable parental consent has not yet been obtained, we will use online contact information (such as an email address) only as is appropriate to:
-	request the name or online contact information of a parent or guardian for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing notification to the parent or guardian;
-	respond directly to the child's request on a one-time basis, not using that information to re-contact the child for any other purpose;
-	respond more than once directly to a specific request from the child (for example, to satisfy the request for a newsletter subscription), not using that information to re-contact the child for any other purpose.
A Notice About External Links:
Occasionally you will find links from UltimateKnicks.com to independently owned, controlled and/or managed websites whose content we or our ad partners believe will be of possible interest and value to our visitors. Additionally you'll see links from advertisers, sponsors and other partners who may use UltimateKnicks.com's logo as part of a co-branding agreement.
In many cases these links represent cooperative projects or mutual links established with the organizations connected with these websites. We don't control the content of these links. These other websites may send you their own cookies, collect data or solicit personal information. We do not control these cookies or the content of these third parties.
UltimateKnicks.com has partnered with other companies to provide certain services. In some cases, while you may see UltimateKnicks.com's logo on another company's website, UltimateKnicks.com does not share any of your personally identifiable information with these partners and they do not share any information with us. Once you leave our servers (you can generally tell where you are by checking the URL in the location bar on your browser), the use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the website you are visiting. That policy may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of these other websites via a link from that website's homepage, you should contact the website directly for more information.
We specifically recommend that children check with their parents or guardians before clicking on to any new websites.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of UltimateKnicks.com or your dealings with UltimateKnicks.com, please email us at info@UltimateKnicks.com.
This Privacy Policy also fully incorporates all of the Terms of Use located here: http://www.UltimateKnicks.com/termsofuse.asp.
©2001-2012 ultimateknicks.comm
All rights reserved. About Us.
This site is not affiliated with the NY Knicks or the National Basketball Association in any way.
You may visit the official NY Knicks web site by clicking here.
All times (GMT-05:00) Eastern Time.
Terms of Use and Privacy Policy
